kullsms.com 2008-09-26

# Company Highlights

In this privacy statement, KULLmessage has disclosed how it uses and treats all data on this website.

Information Collection  
Weblinksms is the sole owner of the information collected on kullmessage.com and kullsms.com. KULLmessage collects information from our users at several different points on our Web sites.

Newsletter  
Optional newsletter services may be provided and withdrawn by KULLmessage at any time. KULLmessage will not pass on your email address for these optional newsletters to any third parties unless specified on the individual newsletter subscription page. You can add/remove yourself from these optional newsletters at any time.

Legal Disclaimer  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. We will make every effort to help the Police services with their enquiries if we believe it is in our users interests and to protect the KULLmessage service.

Third Party Advertisers  
Advertisers may collect information while you are using KULLmessage sites about pages you have viewed, and other viewing details. This helps them provide you with different and interesting adverts on every page you see. KULLmessage does not share additional information with advertisers.

Links  
This Web site might contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, KULLmessage, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by these web sites (KULLmessage.

Notification of Changes  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

Queries/Orders  
Your query and order will be dealt with quickly. Please include a return address, contact telephone number, and alternative email address and allow a maximum of 48 hrs for us to get back to you.

Thank you.
